Speaker: The best thing about the weather in London is that it’s hardly ever extreme.
It isn’t usually very hot or very cold.
In summer, it’s sometimes sunny and sometimes cloudy, with temperatures of about 22 degrees.
And of course, it sometimes rains.
In winter, the temperature is usually between zero and ten degrees.
It can be windy and cold, but it hardly ever snows.
In spring and in autumn the weather is very changeable – you can have all four seasons in one day!
It can be sunny in the morning, cloudy at lunchtime,
raining in the afternoon, and then cold and windy in the evening.
It’s a good idea for tourists to take their sunglasses and their umbrellas when they go out.
One thing you don’t often see these days in London is fog.
A lot of tourists come to London and say,
‘Where’s the fog? London is always foggy in films!’
Well, it’s true that in the past, that is until the 1950s,
London was a very foggy city because the air was really dirty.
But today the air is quite clean and it’s hardly ever foggy.